{
    "id": "c94e30feb51142d4b00b2e8a197e53d7",
    "title": "Articles With Uncountable Nouns",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We need someone with …………………. knowledge of German.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "excellent",
                "an excellent",
                "the excellent"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c536f3547d204818a8f056cfc39a019b"
        },
        {
            "question": "You speak ..................... Hindi.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "perfect",
                "a perfect",
                "the perfect"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a447711abd6f43fb83260cb295f76838"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has ………………….. distrust of strangers.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "deep",
                "a deep",
                "the deep"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c3948f4ed9a249cb81f586bc205b8af7"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is …………………. work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hard",
                "a hard",
                "the hard"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1fd698c2ed9c43eab0343df4dab1b311"
        },
        {
            "question": "My parents gave me ………………….. education.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "a good",
                "the good"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "59b1cc60a2a9469a83c57154e70e91f0"
        },
        {
            "question": "We’ve been having ………………….. weather.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "terrible",
                "a terrible",
                "the terrible"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1ea3c187e96b4390a80b18571888d677"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has ………………… understanding of the subject.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "thorough",
                "a thorough",
                "the thorough"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2fe2056bf5bd4e6fa84b80451dd2c804"
        },
        {
            "question": "She’s in …………………. health.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "a good",
                "the good"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dfb6c9a8103645dfa58dc7a0d8835ac0"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has ………………….. love for his country.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "great",
                "a great",
                "the great"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1b9f46fae8354f6b9bc4e9ef15ba9e02"
        },
        {
            "question": "He caused …………………. for all of us.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "trouble",
                "a trouble",
                "the trouble"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d2c61c3f76694d52ab5289be86a32324"
        }
    ]
}